topcouponstoday.com 2017-05-12

# Privacy Policy | Top Coupons Today

### Privacy Policy - Your Privacy Rights

_Effective Date: May 10, 2012_

### What information does TopCouponsToday.com collect and how does TopCouponsToday.com use it?

This Privacy Policy describes the information practices of the TopCouponsToday.com website, operated by TopCouponsToday.com. You may visit and use certain features of our website without any registration, in which case none of your personal information will be collected or retained. However, if you to register through our website or request coupons, we will ask you to provide personal information such as your contact information and your date of birth.

In addition, some sections of our website allow you to provide information directly to third parties whose websites are framed within our website, as described below in the section on "Third party links and co-brand relationships."

When you visit our website, we may also collect information that does not identify you personally, such as the IP address of the computer making the request, information about your computer and browser, and information about your use of our website.

We use the information we collect to provide you with product promotions, support and any information you request, and otherwise to operate our business and this website.

### How does TopCouponsToday.com protect visitor information?

TopCouponsToday.com uses reasonable security measures to help protect the information that we collect.

### Does TopCouponsToday.com use "cookies"?

We use cookies so that we can help provide our customers with a better and more efficient experience on our website. A "cookie" is a piece of information a web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the web site to remember who you are without personally identifying you. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access all of the features on our website.

### Does TopCouponsToday.com disclose any information it collects from its visitors to third parties?

TopCouponsToday.com may share the information you provide to us with third parties to allow these third parties to contact you and provide you offers and other information that they think will be valuable to you. TopCouponsToday.com does not control the policies or practices of other entities with which we may share data. If you would like to learn about the policies and practices of these third parties or any choices they may offer, you should contact them directly.

TopCouponsToday.com may share your information with our affiliates or with service providers and vendors who work on our behalf, and these third parties may further disclose the information they receive from us. TopCouponsToday.com may use, sell or transfer any anonymous or aggregated statistical user data in any manner at any time. We may also disclose your personal information to protect the Company or our legal rights or when required to do so by law, including in response to a search warrant, subpoena, court order, or request from a law enforcement agency. We may transfer information to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

We serve some third-party ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

TopCouponsToday.com uses one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our Site and third-party sites. Cookies and other technologies such as Web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site, as well as on third-party sites where you may visit. To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other Web sites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous, and does not enable any third-party to identify you individually.

Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your anonymous interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by [clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### What are my choices?

If you would like TopCouponsToday.com to stop providing your information to these third parties, please send a "do not share" request to TopCouponsToday.com by emailing us at [privacy@TopCouponsToday.com](mailto:privacy@TopCouponsToday.com?subject=TopCouponsToday.com%20-%20Privacy%20Question), or by contacting us as directed below under "Additional Information."

### TopCouponsToday.com's special note to parents

TopCouponsToday.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

### Third party links and co-brand relationships

In order to provide increased value to our visitors, TopCouponsToday.com may choose various third party websites to link to and from, and frame within, its own website. TopCouponsToday.com may also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer information, programs and other services and features to its users. A "framed" website is a page from a third party’s website that appears within our website. Framing allows you to interact with a third party website without navigating away from our website.

These third party web sites may independently solicit and collect information from you. TopCouponsToday.com does not control these linked sites. Since their treatment of personal information may differ from ours, we encourage you to carefully review the privacy statements and terms of use of all third party web sites you access. On occasion, those third party web sites may provide us with information about your use of those sites.

### Your consent and changes to this policy

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by TopCouponsToday.com as set forth in this Privacy Statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. Continued access or use of the website shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this Privacy Statement.

### Additional Information

This notice details the privacy policies of TopCouponsToday.com for all of its users of its website with regard to information collected through this website. If you have questions regarding this policy or the practices of TopCouponsToday.com, contact us at TopCouponsToday.com, Privacy Division, located at 156 Beach 9th Street, Far Rockaway, NY 11691

Powered by [TopCouponsToday.com](http://topcouponstoday.com/). This site offers consumers access to free promotional offers. By registering the consumer agrees to receive email annoucements from such advertisers listed in this site. By continuing, you certify that you are a US resident over the age of 18 and that you agree to the privacy policy, participation requirements and End User License Agreement.
